Hi everyone, in today's video, I'm going to show you how to add a wishlist to
your profile.
Go to the adultweb.com website and log in using your username and password.
Once you've logged in, come along the top here and click on More.
And then click here on Wishlist.
Here in the corner, click on Add a Delivery Address and enter in your full
address with
your real name postcode, ECT.
Make sure that everyone's entered correctly and don't worry, this is completely
hidden.
No one else can see your address.
Once you've done that, click Save Address.
I'll just exit because I'm not entered in one at the moment.
Once you've done that, come along here and click on Browse.
Click on Official Stores and here you see all the items that you can add to
your wishlist
and there's a lot that you can go through.
You can search stuff as well on this bar here and you can click on different
things to
look through.
So let's say you want to add this to our wishlist, so we click on here.
You click on Add to Wishlist and here you will name the wishlist, my wishlist,
Add to Wishlist.
And it's saying to now enter an address.
So here you put your address in again.
Once this is done, click Save Address.
So I'm just going to cancel for now as I'm not putting one in, but you need to
put one
in a press Save usually.
And there you go, that's how you add stuff to your wishlist.
To add more, just go back on to how I showed you and you can add more and more
to your
wishlist.
Or just click back here and keep going through the items.